



BRENNON ALLEN

Junior Software Developer

About Me

My tech experience includes Tier 1 & 2 desktop support, LAN & WAN setup: Server configuration, Router & Switch configuration; Computer (re)imaging. Mobile device management, Graphic design, Web development, Digital marketing, Database development, Server development, and more.



+1 726-400-3411



brennon.t.allen@gmail.com



4114 Medical Drive, San Antonio, Texas 78229

Languages

English

Strengths

- HTML
 Express
 Mongoose

- React MongoDB
- Node JavaScript

Character

- Creative
- Resilient
- Thoughtful
- Resolute
- Team Player
- Leader by Example
- Organized
- Introspective

Experience

Founder, Full-Stack Web Developer

Code Tailors | Remote

Aug 2024 - Present

• Founded Code Tailors to conduct web-development projects for small businesses using HTML, CSS, JS, and ReactJS or the front-end coupled with Express, Mongoose, and MongoDB for the back-end.

Junior Computer Systems Engineer / Architect

General Dynamics Information Technology | San Antonio, TX May 2024 - Aug 2024

- Managed a Windows 11 tech refresh for 1,500 users, including imaging and deploying laptops, software management, and Active Directory tasks.
- Handled asset inventory, shipping, and tracking, and conducted user data backup with USMT and OneDrive.

Information Technology Specialist

U.S. Army | Domestic and Foreign Feb 2019 - Feb 2024

- Led a team to support 600+ users across HQ and South America, configuring iOS devices and setting up VTC environments.
- Established a remote WAN site, managing network setup and secure communication at all OSI layers.

Education

University of Phoenix

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Nov 2024 - Present

V-School | Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node, React, Express, Mongoose, MongoDB Mar 2024 - Aug 2024

University of Phoenix

Associate of Arts in Information Technology Feb 2020 - Jun 2021

Interests

Front-End | Responsive, Smooth, Simple Back-End | Logic, Operations, Organization

